Iulian Prodea

iulian.prodea@outlook.com | 07424 693338 https://linkedin.com/in/iulian-pro | https://iulian.pro | https://github.com/iulianpro Willing to relocate across the UK

Personal Profile

Recently graduated with an EQF Level 5 Diploma in Software Development at the Code Institute Ireland. I am now following the passion I have always had for technology and web development hoping to build it to a professional level after a fantastic career in Insurance. I am very determined to become an experienced Developer, I continue to learn new things day by day and I am convinced that I will be able to bring add-value to the organization I will work for and I will be a winning investment for that company.

Key skills

- Excellent organisational and time management skills
- Ability to work calmly under pressure and prioritise work
- Problem solving person
- "Can Do" attitude
- Hardworking
- Attention to details
- Team player
- Keen to learn

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery
- JSON, AJAX, API's
- Python
- Flask and Django Frameworks
- MySQL, MongoDB, SQLite, PostgreSQL
- Amazon Web Services S3
- Heroku, Stripe, Git Version Control, GitHub
- Currently studying PHP

Employment History

Holmleigh Care Homes Ltd

Waking Night Support Care Worker

2019-2020

My duties included:

- Assisting service users with personal care needs including eating, dressing and washing.
- Carrying out domestic duties including cooking and cleaning.
- Creating opportunities for service users to develop personally and with their health.
- Establishing and maintaining personal relationships and social networks.
- Monitoring progress and recording notes on daily record sheets.

S.A.R. City Insurance SA, Romania Area Sales Manager

2012-2019

I previously worked as an Insurance Advisor and Branch Manager before promotion. My duties included:

- Driving sales processes and teams over 25 employees from eight branches from NW of Romania.
- Developing strategies for growing business relationships with the company's partners.
- Recruiting candidates for vacancies.
- Tracking and fulfilling targets goals.

Achievements: Together with the sales teams, I managed to increase the company's client portfolio as well as sales volumes by 30% each year. Previously, I was noticed by the company's management as one of the most productive employees, as proof that the Country Sales Manager proposed me to take over the position of Branch Manager and then the Area Sales Manager role.

Education

Code Institute, Ireland 2019-2020

EQF Level 5 Diploma, Full Stack Software Developer (http://bit.ly/iulianpro-diploma)

- User Centric Frontend Development:
 - HTML Fundamentals
 - CSS Fundamentals
 - Bootstrap 4
 - GitHub
 - Git Version Control
 - VS Code
 - Project: https://iulianpro.github.io/my-city/
- Interactive Frontend Development:
 - JavaScript
 - jQuery
 - JSON
 - DOM Manipulation
 - Google Maps API's
 - Project: https://iulianpro.github.io/discover-transylvania/
- ♣ Data Centric Development:
 - Databases Fundamentals
 - Python Fundamentals
 - SQL and noSQL
 - MySQL
 - Manipulated data with Python
 - Flask Framework
 - MongoDB
 - CRUD Operations
 - Project https://iulianpro-shifts-manager.herokuapp.com/
- ♣ Full Stack Frameworks with Django:
 - Django Framework
 - Stripe
 - Amazon Web Services (S3)
 - Project https://iulianpro-give-help.herokuapp.com/

References available upon request.